and the last thing I remember her achieving
is graduating high school.
At 20, she dropped out of college because she was pregnant.
She moved in with the father,
and for 10 years they were a family.
All that time she didn't had a job
even when her sons started school.
Those two never married,
and he left her about two years ago.
She is now pregnant again,
new dad isn't involved,
works at fast food and barely scraps by.
She is constantly asking for money.
She actually wanted to move in with me and my kids.
My wife travels a lot.
I have two daughters,
and my sister told me she wanted to be closer.
She wanted to move into my home,
that it would be good for the girls to have a women
they could look up to.
She never liked that my wife travels.
This isn't the first time she has brought it up,
and I have turned her down politely many times.
My sister brought it up again last night.
I told her no.
This resulted in a heated conversation
with her asking why.
I decided to be honest,
and I told her that she isn't the type of women
I want my kids to look up to.
I also listed the reasons above.
She called me a jerk.
The family is now on my ass about this,
saying I was heartless to tell her that.
They also want me to apologize.
Am I the asshole?